[{"answer": "Your royal highness.", "docId": "110220pmt", "aSentId": 3, "question": "What will I call you?", "qSentId": 2}, {"answer": "By divine right if you must.", "docId": "110220pmt", "aSentId": 25, "question": "By what right?", "qSentId": 24}, {"answer": "Because I have a right.", "docId": "110220pmt", "aSentId": 31, "question": "Why should I waste my time listening?", "qSentId": 30}, {"answer": "That will have to be for others to decide or for me to decide when I'm so old that I'm other -- it'll be in knotting away trying to grasp at any memories I have dictating my memoirs.", "docId": "110220pmt", "aSentId": 43, "question": "Do you think it is?", "qSentId": 42}, {"answer": "I found the most -- I fell in love with him completely.", "docId": "110220pmt", "aSentId": 51, "question": "What did you think of Bertie, of King George VI?", "qSentId": 50}, {"answer": "It is.", "docId": "110220pmt", "aSentId": 57, "question": "I've actually heard some of the real footage of King George VI, and it's painful listening, isn't it?", "qSentId": 56}, {"answer": "When I'm in a supermarket, yes.", "docId": "110220pmt", "aSentId": 70, "question": "When you're in the supermarket, and you're trying to order something, do you lapse into Bertie, just start stammering because you just got so used to that voice?", "qSentId": 69}, {"answer": "Well, I thought I was lucky.", "docId": "110220pmt", "aSentId": 91, "question": "Aren't we both lucky?", "qSentId": 90}, {"answer": "I do relish that.", "docId": "110220pmt", "aSentId": 116, "question": "Do you quite like the fact of having been Darcy and having been in \"Bridget Jones'\" stuff where you play the classic archetype of charmer that the last two great roles you've had, \"Single Man\" and \"King's Speech,\" you're not actually playing that kind of character?", "qSentId": 115}, {"answer": "Of course.", "docId": "110220pmt", "aSentId": 120, "question": "You prefer it as an actor?", "qSentId": 119}, {"answer": "Leave me taking out the trash.", "docId": "110220pmt", "aSentId": 158, "question": "But where does that leave you?", "qSentId": 157}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110220pmt", "aSentId": 161, "question": "Is she amused by your sex symbol image?", "qSentId": 160}, {"answer": "She's Italian.", "docId": "110220pmt", "aSentId": 168, "question": "She's Italian, of course?", "qSentId": 167}, {"answer": "(Speaking in foreign language)", "docId": "110220pmt", "aSentId": 172, "question": "How's your Italian?", "qSentId": 171}, {"answer": "Not personally, no.", "docId": "110220pmt", "aSentId": 183, "question": "Do you think all -- you know, do you find John Major sexy?", "qSentId": 182}, {"answer": "We don't go there.", "docId": "110220pmt", "aSentId": 203, "question": "When we come back, what's the biggest turkey?", "qSentId": 202}, {"answer": "IRTH: You know, I -- we've made it 15 years together.", "docId": "110220pmt", "aSentId": 242, "question": "Any kind of normality in that relationship?", "qSentId": 241}, {"answer": "It does help to actually realize that however stunning the person who's, you know, fluttering eyelashes at you is she doesn't do anything to match up to your wife.", "docId": "110220pmt", "aSentId": 255, "question": "How do you avoid the shallow pitfalls of temptation like a thrown Hollywood heartthrob away?", "qSentId": 254}, {"answer": "Oh, yes.", "docId": "110220pmt", "aSentId": 271, "question": "And you don't really talk about them much, but as they get older, your children, would it unnerve you if they wanted to go into acting?", "qSentId": 270}, {"answer": "Well, he's still around.", "docId": "110220pmt", "aSentId": 276, "question": "What would he have made of your success?", "qSentId": 275}, {"answer": "Apparently.", "docId": "110220pmt", "aSentId": 288, "question": "Have I?", "qSentId": 287}, {"answer": "We don't go there.", "docId": "110220pmt", "aSentId": 292, "question": "What's the biggest turkey?", "qSentId": 291}, {"answer": "We can't, you see.", "docId": "110220pmt", "aSentId": 303, "question": "What's the worst?", "qSentId": 302}, {"answer": "Because --", "docId": "110220pmt", "aSentId": 305, "question": "Why not?", "qSentId": 304}, {"answer": "Spectacular.", "docId": "110220pmt", "aSentId": 319, "question": "It's amazing, isn't it?", "qSentId": 318}, {"answer": "You can have two.", "docId": "110220pmt", "aSentId": 322, "question": "Can I have all of them?", "qSentId": 321}, {"answer": "I like the idea of them.", "docId": "110220pmt", "aSentId": 333, "question": "Do you like to do love scenes?", "qSentId": 332}, {"answer": "ORGAN: This is what I'm thinking.", "docId": "110220pmt", "aSentId": 338, "question": "Do you think no one would notice if you stepped in as a body double?", "qSentId": 337}, {"answer": "I doubt it.", "docId": "110220pmt", "aSentId": 363, "question": "I mean can any wife enjoy watching their beloved husband romping with Scarlet Johansson?", "qSentId": 362}, {"answer": "I would describe him as my geisha girl.", "docId": "110220pmt", "aSentId": 379, "question": "But if you were to introduce him yourself, how would you describe him?", "qSentId": 378}, {"answer": "Oh, I'm doing a film about Humpty Dumpty down here.", "docId": "110220pmt", "aSentId": 413, "question": "Where is your hair?", "qSentId": 412}, {"answer": "Well, we --", "docId": "110220pmt", "aSentId": 419, "question": "How would you describe your relationship with Colin?", "qSentId": 418}, {"answer": "Oh.", "docId": "110220pmt", "aSentId": 427, "question": "Do you believe in the royal family?", "qSentId": 426}, {"answer": "I have briefly met Prince Charles and I think he's a very, very interesting, very civil and civilized person.", "docId": "110220pmt", "aSentId": 434, "question": "Have you met any of them?", "qSentId": 433}, {"answer": "I like really voting.", "docId": "110220pmt", "aSentId": 439, "question": "Do you think the institution is a good one?", "qSentId": 438}, {"answer": "It is a problem for me, yes.", "docId": "110220pmt", "aSentId": 443, "question": "Unelected institution isn't really your cup of tea?", "qSentId": 442}, {"answer": "I'll let that one drift over to Australia.", "docId": "110220pmt", "aSentId": 470, "question": "Have you had a private bet between each other as to who may actually walk away with the old statue?", "qSentId": 469}, {"answer": "I think Helena Bonham Carter will get it, and Colin and I won't, and will be furious.", "docId": "110220pmt", "aSentId": 472, "question": "Geoffrey?", "qSentId": 471}, {"answer": "It's a post modernist experience I think, Piers.", "docId": "110220pmt", "aSentId": 477, "question": "Is it as nerve wrecking as I imagine it would be?", "qSentId": 476}, {"answer": "Your poisonous words.", "docId": "110220pmt", "aSentId": 494, "question": "What are you so afraid of?", "qSentId": 493}, {"answer": "That -- that credit, I think, is more on the creative side.", "docId": "110220pmt", "aSentId": 505, "question": "What was Colin like to work for, in terms of him working to you as a producer?", "qSentId": 504}, {"answer": "Very well.", "docId": "110220pmt", "aSentId": 517, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 516}, {"answer": "I'm very well.", "docId": "110220pmt", "aSentId": 519, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 518}, {"answer": "Yeah, I did, actually, when I was very, very young, a long, long time ago, at the premier of \"A Room With a View.", "docId": "110220pmt", "aSentId": 522, "question": "Did you ever meet the queen mother?", "qSentId": 521}, {"answer": "They talk a lot.", "docId": "110220pmt", "aSentId": 564, "question": "The two heavily-ego'd movie stars?", "qSentId": 563}, {"answer": "Yes, the Duke of York.", "docId": "110220pmt", "aSentId": 616, "question": "Duke of York?", "qSentId": 615}, {"answer": "You will be if you remain unobliging.", "docId": "110220pmt", "aSentId": 623, "question": "Am I considered the enemy?", "qSentId": 622}, {"answer": "But then ask him.", "docId": "110220pmt", "aSentId": 631, "question": "Have you, Geoffrey?", "qSentId": 630}, {"answer": "Don't know.", "docId": "110220pmt", "aSentId": 648, "question": "What are your early thoughts, Helena?", "qSentId": 647}, {"answer": "I did fancy him in his uniform, with the medals.", "docId": "110220pmt", "aSentId": 687, "question": "But what are your views on Colin Firth the sex symbol?", "qSentId": 686}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110220pmt", "aSentId": 689, "question": "Do you remember that?", "qSentId": 688}, {"answer": "Yeah, yeah, I did, I did.", "docId": "110220pmt", "aSentId": 691, "question": "You like him as Darcy?", "qSentId": 690}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110220pmt", "aSentId": 703, "question": "Would you fancy Piers in the same uniform?", "qSentId": 702}, {"answer": "To see a woman come out who is a 48-year-old spinster in a tiny Scottish village, and everyone's laughing at here, and she's able to sing like Elaine Page, and we're all sniggering and everything else.", "docId": "110220pmt", "aSentId": 725, "question": "Wasn't it?", "qSentId": 724}, {"answer": "You know, the thing that happens with this age -- this extraordinary advanced age I've reached is that it's not the long-term memory going.", "docId": "110220pmt", "aSentId": 733, "question": "If Susan Boyle was here now Colin, singing \"I Dreamed a Dream,\" would you dream involve the Academy Awards end of February, standing there clutching the gong, making the speech you've been preparing and practicing for probably 40 years?", "qSentId": 732}, {"answer": "I don't know how much one even really dares to contemplates dreams on that scale, really.", "docId": "110220pmt", "aSentId": 745, "question": "Is it the pinnacle?", "qSentId": 744}, {"answer": "IRTH: Yeah, go on, darling.", "docId": "110220pmt", "aSentId": 753, "question": "Can I chip in here?", "qSentId": 752}, {"answer": "He couldn't have been king without her.", "docId": "110220pmt", "aSentId": 757, "question": "How could we forget?", "qSentId": 756}]